internet-khazana.com 2013-06-11

# Privacy Policy

## [Privacy Policy](http://www.internet-khazana.com/blog/privacy-policy/ "Privacy Policy")

## Contact US : admin@Internet-Khazana.com

The privacy of my visitors to Internet-Khazana.com is important to me.

At Internet-Khazana.com, I recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information I receive and collect when you use visit Internet-Khazana.com, and how I safeguard your information.

I never sell any kind of personal information to third parties or use this data for any illegal activities.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, I collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Time Warner), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited my site and which pages you visit.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

I do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit this site.

I use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Los Angeles restaurants to Los Angeles residents, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing web development ads to someone who frequents web design sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.

However, this can affect how you are able to interact with my site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Google AdSense

The Google’s AdSense program uses the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables this site to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Email Addresses

Should you contact me or subscribe to any of my information services via email, I will never sell or give away your email address.
